Blackberry Smoke乐队 演奏“Waiting for the Thunder”（等待雷鸣）
♪ Light the fuse and run now, brother ♪
♪ 'Cause you ain't got a lot of time ♪
♪ Don't you act surprised ♪
♪ When it all goes to hell ♪
♪ On your dime ♪
♪ Maybe you can stand tall enough ♪
♪ To look the Devil eye to eye ♪
♪ But you better make your getaway quick ♪
哇哦 来吧
Whoo, come on!
♪ So you don't have ♪
♪ To answer why ♪
♪ The bells will ring ♪
♪ And the flames will fly ♪
♪ 2,000 years of fury ♪
♪ In the big black sky ♪
♪ The wind will blow ♪
♪ And the rain will fall ♪
♪ Are we waiting for the thunder ♪
♪ Or will the lightning get us all? ♪
NCIS 新奥尔良 S03E07
如果你的宝宝不睡觉或是整晚在哭
If your toddler doesn't sleep and cries all night,
让你处于
it might very well be gas
精神崩溃边缘的
that has you on the verge
很可能是胀气
of a nervous breakdown.
首先 抱起你的宝宝
First, pick him or her up,
肚子冲下 轻轻拍打
stomach down, gently patting...
有点像橄榄球 对吗
Kind of like a football, right?
然后你轻轻地拍打他
And you pat him gently.
你甚至可以晃晃他
You can even rock him
一圈一圈地来
going round and round in circles,
像搅拌一大锅汤
like stirring a big pot of soup.
晃呀 晃呀 晃呀晃
Bob, bob, bob, bob.
哦 他长大后会变成什么
Aw, what's he gonna be when he grows up?
一个篮球吗
A basketball?
如果这样还不行的话
If all this doesn't help...
脸 头发 橄榄球
Face. Hair. Football.
家庭生活很甜蜜呀
Take it family life's just peachy.
一周前 家里就只有我一个人
A week ago, it was just me at the house.
现在多了一个整夜在哭 让我无法睡觉的孩子
Now I got a crying toddler keeping me up at night
和一个我不怎么了解的妈妈
and a mama I barely know.
你对她的了解已经能生出个孩子了
You knew her well enough to make the toddler.
还有 她每分钟都会给我发信息
Plus, she keeps texting me every minute.
"买吸管杯 买尿布
"Pick up sippy cups, pick up diapers.
买这个 买那个"
Pick up this, pick up that."
我连吸管杯是什么都不知道
I don't even know what a sippy cup is.
你是在寻求我的建议吗
Is this you asking me for advice?
因为 通常
Because, normally,
我是很乐于助人的 Lasalle 真的
I'd love to help, Lasalle, I really would,
但我很快就要回华盛顿的家了
but I'm back home in DC in about a minute and a half.
问题在于 你是唯一知道这件事的人
Except the problem is, you're the only one that knows.
没错
Right.
这确实是个问题
That is the problem.
有点尴尬 你不觉得吗
It's a little awkward, don't you think?
我以为你现在已经
I mean, I thought you would have told Country Mouse
告诉了那个"乡下鼠"
about it by now.
我才是"乡下鼠" 好吗
I'm Country Mouse, all right?
-Percy 她是"城里鼠" -你知道吗
- Percy, she's City Mouse. - You know what?
你应该和Pride谈谈这件事
You ought to talk to Pride about this.
他可以给你比菲尔博士更有用的建议
That man's got more homespun advice than Dr. Phil.
菲尔·麦格劳：著名电视心理学咨询专家，主持著名访谈类节目"菲尔博士"
我听说他有一个女儿 成长得挺好
I heard he's got a daughter; she turned out all right.
呦呦呦 大家好
Yo, yo, yo, what's up?
Percy 嗨 你好
Percy, hey. What's up?
什么情况
What's up?
发生了什么
What's going on?
没什么
Nothing.
嗯 哼
Uh... huh?
和Pride谈谈
Talk to Pride.
-早上好 Sonja -嗨
- Morning, Sonja. - Hey.
-你做的够两个人喝吗 -当然
- You making enough for two? - Sure.
我来吧
I got it.
哦 好的
Oh, great.
你有心事吗
Something on your mind?
没有 我很好
No, I'm good.
你能告诉我 Lasalle怎么了吗
Okay, can you tell me what's wrong with Lasalle?
他紧张兮兮的 一直收到很多短信
He's jumpy, he's getting these texts.
他就像个僵尸 但他不肯告诉我怎么回事
He looks like a zombie, but he won't tell me about it.
最近看上去确实有点不对劲
Does seem a little bit distracted lately.
是啊 所以
Right. So.
"Pride谈话"安排在什么时候
When's the “Pride talking to" scheduled?
不是这么来的
Doesn't work like that.
当他准备好了
He'll come around
-他会来找我 -准备好了 好了
- when he's ready. - Ready, ready, right.
现在的情况是 他已经告诉了那位FBI的人
See, the thing is, he already told FBI.
她很显然知道这件事 所以
She's obviously hip to it, so...
我觉得他准备好了
I think he's ready.
Pride
Pride.
好 好的
Okay... Okay.
得带上咖啡走了
Got to get the coffee to go.
圣玛丽公园有一名海军死了
We got a dead sailor by St. Mary's Park.
Loretta在那呢
There's Loretta.
新鲜的菊苣汁
Fresh chicory...
希望你告诉我你知道的一切
in hopes that you will tell me all you know.
行贿就不必了 Dwayne
Bribery's not needed, Dwayne.
但鼓励一下还是很乐意的
But it's always happily encouraged.
街对面有一个很吵的摩托车节
So, across the street a rowdy motorcycle rally,
源于欧洲的年度国际事件，通常持续七天
聚集了上千个"无法无天"的人
thousands of "American outlaws" in town.
有人伤亡 我是真的不意外
Can't say I didn't expect a casualty,
只不过没想到会是你的案子
just didn't expect it to be yours.
受害者叫Lloyd Fillibert
Well, the Vic is Lloyd Fillibert.
一级建筑海军士官 驻扎在密西西比的Gulfport
BU1 stationed in Gulfport, Mississippi.
有一份Oasis旅馆的文件
There's paperwork from the Oasis Motel.
距离摩托车周的庆祝场地几英尺远
Feet away from Bike Week's festival grounds.
海军工兵在美国南部
Seabee was visiting for the biggest
参加最大的摩托车节
motorcycle rally in the South.
问题在于
Question is...
一个比赛怎么会死人呢
how'd the ride turn deadly?
基本情况如下
Well, here's the basics.
一个小口径子弹
It's a small caliber round.
从胸腔后面射入
It entered through the rear of the rib cage,
穿透了这位可怜人的心脏
perforated the poor soul's heart.
一枪毙命
It was a clean shot.
很快就死了
Was dead in seconds.
从细节来看
That kind of an eye for detail,
这不是一起意外的枪击事件
we're not looking at an accidental shooting.
不排除公路暴怒
Try road rage.
指司机之间因驾驶问题而极度愤怒或动粗
警方说 受害者当时在排队参加街头赛车
NOPD tells us your Vic was lined up for a street race.
这就可以解释那些焦橡胶了
Well, that would explain the burnt rubber.
我估计有 20个摩托手吧
I'm guessing maybe... 20 bikers?
如果Fillibert是被近距离射杀
And if Fillibert was shot at close range...
凶手就在他们之中
The killer was one of them.
摩托车赛在新奥尔良举行
Motorcycle race goes down in New Orleans,
应该会有围观者 Chris
there's gonna be onlookers, Chris.
我已经排查过了
Well, I already checked.
目击者们要么逃离了现场
Either the witnesses fled from the scene
要么就是选择性失忆了
or they have a case of selective memory.
可能是怕会出卖不该得罪的帮派
May have been afraid to rat on the wrong club.
摩托帮派无所不在
MCs can go anywhere
从无害的业余体力劳动者
from harmless weekend warriors
到复杂的犯罪集团
to elaborate crime syndicates.
我在ATF知道的
Seen my share at ATF to know.
酒精烟草枪支管理局
保持沉默是明智的
It's smart to keep quiet.
受害者是兄弟连的成员
Victim was a member of the Brothers at Arms.
这个帮派在新奥尔良有很长的历史了
Club's got a long-standing history in New Orleans.
成立之初有一个崇高的想法
Started as an honorable idea.
被剥夺权利的老兵们没有家和人生目标
Disenfranchised vets without home or purpose
他们联合起来重建家园和人生目标
banded together to give them both.
本是卡特里娜飓风之后做好事的
Supposed to do good after Katrina.
但是
But...
其它帮派不让他们到自己的地盘
Others didn't want them on their turf.
没错 因为那块地盘是骑行帮
Yeah, 'cause the turf belonged to the Niners.
这个骑行帮不干好事
Bad motorcycle gang.
交易毒品 走私武器
Drug dealing, trafficking weapons...
我在ATF的时候追查过他们
I used to go after them when I was with ATF.
想把他们一网打尽 可最后发现
Tried to root them out, but turned out
这个组织的根基非常牢固
they were too well entrenched.
是的 还很聪明
Yeah, smart, too.
不知用了什么手段 让那帮老兵看起来像是坏人
Somehow made the vets look like they were the bad guys.
当时有些人认为
Didn't help back then that some folks thought
所有的老兵都是残缺和暴力的
all vets were damaged goods and violent.
即便他们真的是去帮忙重建 也没能改变这种想法吗
Even though they were really here to help rebuild?
骑行帮把他们视作威胁 只想让他们离开
Niners viewed them as a threat, just wanted them gone.
让他们卷入斗殴 无辜的人受了伤
Sucked them into a fight, innocent people got hurt,
而那些老兵们为一切的动乱
and the vets took the blame
背了黑锅
for all the unrest.
这座城市 太轻易评判
The city... quick to judge,
-所以他们离开了 -而现在
- so they left. - And now this
这是一个温暖的欢迎仪式 说曹操曹操就到
for a warm welcome. Speak of the devil.
骑行帮的人来了
There's the Niners right there.
哦
Oh.
他没看见我吧
He didn't spot me, did he?
谁
Who?
我想她说的是那个小帅哥
I think she's talking about the cute guy,
机车上的纹身男 27岁左右的约翰尼·德普
tribals on a tank, Johnny Depp circa 1990.
1963年生的美国影视演员
我猜你认识他吧
Know him I take it?
对 算是吧
Yeah, sort of.
他曾经是ATF的线人
He was an ATF informant.
Ramon
Ramon.
Ramon?
他是骑行帮的人吗
Is he a Niner?
不 他以前制造过
No, he used to build
定制摩托车 至少以前是
custom bikes... or at least he used to.
他很可能是来参加摩托车节的
He's probably here for the rally.
好吧
Okay.
Percy Gregorio 深挖两个帮派
Percy, Gregorio, deep-dive both clubs,
告诉我们所有相关人员的情况
get us caught up on everybody involved.
我和Chris去查明
Chris and I are gonna go figure out
受害者的情况
what happened to the victim.
看看是谁想杀死他
See who'd want
以及原因
him dead and why.
别把车刮了 北方佬
Don't scratch it, Yankee.
怎么啦
What?
过于随意的回答
Overly casual response,
单边耸肩
one-sided shoulder shrug,
声音低沉
lowered voice.
我看到这些就知道是在掩饰
I know a good cover when I see it.
你说啥
I'm sorry?
得了吧 帅哥线人 Ramon
Oh, please, hot informant, Ramon?
我是个侧写员
I'm a profiler,
记得吗
remember?
记得 明显不是个很好的侧写员
Yeah, obviously not a good one.
我来开车
I'm driving.
我不是喜欢打听的人
I'm not one to pry,
Christopher
Christopher.
这不关我的事
It's none of my business...
除非影响到了工作
unless it's something that affects work,
但如果你遇到了什么事 需要
but you got something going on and you need
谈谈的话
to talk...
我能搞定 King
I can handle it, King.
别担心
Don't worry.
我不是在担心
I'm not worrying.
只是 有需要可以找我
Just... here if you need me.
好吧 不过这可能需要长谈
Well... just might be a... bigger conversation is all.
我还在
I'm still...
试着解决它
trying to sort it all out and...
我想以正确的方式
I want to do this
来解决
the right way.
想听听建议 不过
Keep an open mind, but...
具体点会更有帮助
Specifics would be helpful.
我想我可能做爸爸了 King
I think I might be a dad, King.
或者说
Or I mean...
我做爸爸了
I am a dad.
我对此一无所知 直到
I had no idea until this...
这个女人带着孩子出现
woman shows up with a baby boy.
哦
Oh.
没错 就是这样
Yeah, exactly.
像我说的 说来话长
Like I said, a bigger conversation.
我们到了
Well, we're here.
等会再说
Hold that thought.
老兵们像是要去什么地方
Vets look like they're going somewhere.
暂时还没出发
Not yet they're not.
别紧张 Chris 你在老兵面前
Now, easy, Chris. You come up on the vets
先拔枪的话
barrel first,
就不可能得到配合了
lose any chance of cooperation.
相信我
Trust me.
哦 你现在对我们亮徽章了
Oh, you badging us now?
Hogan队长
Captain Hogan.
我的搭档
My partner,
Christopher Lasalle
Christopher Lasalle.
到这里
Not here
不是来逮捕的 只是
to arrest anyone, just...
只是想谈谈
just want to talk.
你怎么样 很久没见了
How you been? A long time.
还没久到忘记
Well, not long enough to forget how cops
我们的一个兄弟被杀后
come investigating us
警察是怎么调查我们的
when it's one of our own getting killed.
城市派你们来赶我们走吗 Pride
City sent you to make us leave, Pride?
很多事情做错了 我承认
A lot of things went wrong, I admit.
没错 我们像一群罪犯一样
Yeah, it did. We got chased out of town like a bunch
被人赶出城里 这都是因为
of criminals all because
新奥尔良警方不敢将真正的罪犯绳之以法
NOPD was too afraid to take on the real outlaws.
我们不是新奥尔良警局的警察
We're not NOPD.
我们是来问点事情的
Here for information,
不是来控告谁的
not accusations.
我们需要知道你们为什么回来
Need to know why you came back.
好吗 这也许能帮我们查出是谁杀了你们的人
Okay? It might help us find out who killed your man.
省点纳税人的钱吧 警长
Save the tax dollars, Sheriff.
骑行帮杀了Fillibert 就这么简单
Niners killed Fillibert. Easy as that.
你怎么如此确定
And how are you so sure?
我们帮是回来参加摩托车节的
My club came back for the rally.
原以为十年过去了 我们也许可以重新开始
Thought after ten years, maybe we'd start over,
这个地方依然需要重建
places still need rebuilding.
我们在还没过州界的时候
Barely crossed state line 'fore we hear
就听说骑行帮在计划着什么事
that the Niners are planning something.
肯定是他们中的一个
Now, one of 'em must've
说服他去参加他们的比赛
convinced him to run in their race
作为和解
as a-a peace offering.
结果Fillibert就被杀了
Got Fillibert shot instead.
他在参加骑行帮的比赛吗
He was racing the Niners?
包围着他 十比一 然后他们中的一个杀了他
Surrounded him, ten to one. Then one of them killed him.
这次我不会等法律来
I'm not waiting on the law to do the right thing
-主持公道了 -好吧
- this time. - Okay,
你们想重新开始吧
you want to make a fresh start?
你们不想被称作罪犯吧
You don't want to be called criminals?
如果你们出去报复他们
You go out there, retaliate,
你们就真成罪犯了
that's all you're gonna be.
我知道你们曾经被不公正地对待
Know you've been mistreated in the past.
这不会改变什么
That doesn't make this right.
你得给我个机会 Hogan
Got to give me a chance here, Hogan.
让我们来调查是谁杀了你的人
Let us find out who killed your man.
我们会将他绳之以法
We'll bring him to justice.
你最好说到做到
You better.
你还是应该
Still, you should probably
找个时间告诉Percy发生了什么
tell Percy what's going on at some point.
她很担心 希望你没事
She's concerned, hopes you're okay.
我知道应该告诉她
Hey, I know I should.
但我怕她会鄙视我的愚蠢
But I'm scared Percy's gonna whup my butt for being stupid.
有可能
Well, she might.
听着 这事不好办
Listen, this is a tough one.
你会解决好的
You'll figure it out.
好了 关于骑行帮
All right. About the Niners.
-嗯 -我知道他们有
- Yeah. - I know they got
犯罪前科 而且他们和老兵之间
a rap sheet and there's a lot of bad blood
有不少不怀好意的人
between them and the vets,
但你真的认为Fillibert的死
but do you really think Fillibert's the casualty
-是因为十年的仇恨吗 -很难
- of a ten-year-old grudge? - It's hard
不让人那么想 基于他被杀的方式和地点
not to consider it, based on how and where he was killed.
还有 你凭什么认为骑行帮的人会和我们谈
Still, why do you think the Niners are gonna talk to us?
因为他们不希望在他们与老兵们的事情之外
'Cause they don't want the law up and in their business
再牵扯更多法律纠纷
any more than they do the vets.
我只知道我们得
All I know is we got to figure out
在事情升温以前
what's going on
弄清楚发生了什么
before things escalate.
谢了 队长 非常感谢
Thanks, Chief. Appreciate it.
消防队长排除了
Marshal's ruling out
意外爆炸的可能
any accidental explosion.
Sebastian在里面快勘验完了 可能有些发现
Sebastian's almost done inside, thinks he might have something.
-伤亡人数多少 -五人 其中两人有生命危险
- How many casualties? - Five, two critical.
全是骑行帮的成员吗
All Niners?
是的 很明显他们当时在里面开会
Yeah, apparently they were holding a meeting inside.
这说明 干这事的人
Which means whoever did this...
知道他们会在这儿
Knew they'd be here.
我知道你不想听 但是 King 也许是老兵
I know you don't want to hear it, King, but maybe the vets...
-可能是他们自己主持正义 -我知道
- Could've taken justice in their own hands. - I know.
但这说不通
Doesn't make sense, though.
如果Hogan已经计划好这么做
If Hogan had already planned this,
为什么让我们过来 目击这一切
why send us over here so we could see it all?
嘿 就是你
Hey! You!
现在这个样子 你们要怎么处理
What are you gonna do about this, huh?
对做这事的混蛋们 你们抓还是不抓
You gonna arrest these bastards or not?
Morrow
Morrow.
-你认识他吗 -骑行帮的头儿
- You know him? Leader of the Niners.
你需要冷静下来 别急
You need to calm down, take it easy.
你知道你负责这件案子
I figured it'd be you working on this case.
还是像十年前那样 你我都清楚是谁做的
Just like ten years ago, huh? Both know damn well who did it.
我们不会过早下结论 就像我们也不会过早判定
We're not jumping to conclusions, just like we're not jumping to conclusions
是谁枪杀了他们的人
about who shot one of their men either.
你在保护他们吗
You protecting them?
是这样吗 就因为他们是老兵吗
Is that what this is? Just because they're vets?
-这和他们是老兵无关 -嘿
- This has nothing to do with them being... - Hey!
嘿 我们来控制这件事
Hey, hey. We got it under control.
行吗
All right?
所以 麻烦你退后
So, why don't you just back off?
他应该感到感激 他很幸运活下来了
He ought to be more grateful. He's lucky to be alive.
你发现了什么 Sebastian
What'd you find, Sebastian?
大部分是弹片
Uh, mostly shrapnel.
看上去像是来自某种引爆装置
Looks like it came from some kind of detonator.
我认为是简易爆炸装置
I'm thinking improvised explosives device.
简易爆炸装置
IED.
关于爆炸物有什么发现
Anything on the explosives?
有 实际上 我最后又用了
Yeah. Matter of fact, got to finally use
我的激光诱导分解光谱
my laser-induced breakdown spectroscope again.
检测出了现场的爆炸物
It identifies explosives on site.
还实现了我这辈子使用激光枪的梦想
Also fulfills my lifelong dream of wielding a laser gun.
-它到底检测出了什么 -这个嘛
- What exactly did it identify? - Well,
硝化甘油基底 吸附剂和稳定剂
given the nitroglycerin base, sorbents, and stabilizers,
像是老式的炸药
it looks like old-school dynamite.
现在只用来爆破
Used mostly just for demolition these days.
的确爆破了
Demolished it is.
说说情况
Tell me things.
有好消息和坏消息
Well, there's good news and bad news.
就不让你选了
Gonna spare you the choice.
ATF依然把骑行帮划为摩托车帮派
ATF still classifies the Niners as a motorcycle gang.
现在他们中的两人被指控谋杀
Two of 'em are up on murder charges as we speak.
FBI还开展了诱捕行动
FBI also shows several attempted sting ops
针对诈骗指控
on racketeering charges,
虽然目前还没什么收获
though nothing's stuck so far.
老兵那边有什么发现
Anything on the vets?
好消息 除了几次酒吧斗殴以外
That's the good news. Other than a few bar fights,
他们没有犯罪记录
they check out clean.
没错 实际上 市政厅记录显示
Yeah, in fact, city hall shows
Fillbert在半年前获得了一项许可
Fillibert pulled up a permit six months ago.
显然老兵们当时计划帮助修建
Apparently the vets were planning to help build
位于Broadmoor的低价住房
affordable housing in Broadmoor.
Broadmoor就是十年前
Broadmoor's where they tried
-他们要盖房子的地方 -是的
- to build ten years ago. - Yeah.
就在那个混蛋偷了卡特琳娜飓风基金后
Right after that jerk stole the Katrina funds.
McKinley
McKinley.
你怎么知道McKinley
How do you know about McKinley?
说来话长
Long story.
有没有可能是
Any chance
Fillbert的许可给了老兵们
Fillibert's permit gave the vets access
获得爆破炸药的途径
to demolition explosives?
正在查
Looking into it.
有了 显示有上周的提货单 为什么
Here. Shows the order of a pickup last week. Why?
那是炸了骑行帮店铺的炸药吗
That what blew up the Niners' shop?
你觉得这是老兵为Fillibert报仇吗
You thinking the vets retaliated for Fillibert?
所有线索都指向这个方向
Every sign's pointing in that direction.
只是 那说不通啊
It just... doesn't make sense though.
看看Loretta在Fillibert的尸检中有什么发现
See where Loretta's at on Fillibert's autopsy.
也许我们可以把子弹与枪匹配起来
Maybe we can match bullet to gun.
Chris会去医院 调查受害者们知道些什么
Chris'll go to the hospital, find out what the vics know.
-你回办公室吗 -不了
- Coming back to the squad room? - No.
我再去拜访老兵 这次要带着搜查令去
Pay another visit to the vets. This time with a warrant.
我们得抓紧 在事情失控之前
We need to hustle here. Bring in Fillibert's killer
抓到杀死FIllibert和制造爆炸的凶手
and the bomber before things get out of control.
谢谢
Thanks.
嘿 你在这里做什么
Hey! What are you doing here?
你应该去抓住杀死Fillibert的凶手
You are supposed to be arresting Fillibert's killer!
我还在调查此案
I'm still investigating that.
同时也在调查骑行帮店铺爆炸案的凶手
Also investigating who blew up the Niners' bike shop.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
但愿这话是真的
Well, I hope that's true.
因为很多人都受伤了
'Cause a lot of people got hurt.
我现在只知道
All I know so far is that, uh,
那里用过爆破炸药
demolition explosives were used over there.
噢 又急着下结论了 是吗
Oh, jumping to conclusions again, huh?
就像其他警察一样
Par the course for you people.
只是在收集证据
Just gathering evidence.
但我得告诉你
But I got to tell you,
如果你和你的人没有这么做
if you or your boys didn't do it,
就是有人用心良苦 让一切看起来像是你们做的
somebody's working awful hard to make it look like you did.
也许 是又历史重演了吗
Maybe, uh, history repeating itself again?
也许吧 证明你们没有做的唯一方法
Maybe. Only way to prove you didn't retaliate, though,
就是确定两边的炸药不匹配
is to make sure that the explosives don't match.
证据 让你们摆脱嫌疑
Evidence. That'll square you away.
你有搜查令吗
You got a warrant?
我需要搜查令吗
Do I need one?
看好了
There you go.
为了以防万一 我带着呢
I brought one just in case.
现在我们已经说清楚了
Just so we're clear.
如果两边的炸药匹配
If this comes back a match,
下次我会带着逮捕令过来
next time I'll come back with arrest warrants.
只是聊聊
Just saying,
-你知道我知道了 -我知道你知道什么了
- you know I know. - I know you know what?
有关这个Ramon
That there's more to this Ramon thing
你有事瞒着没说 而你越假装没事
than you're letting on to, and the more you pretend
我越肯定有事
there's not, the more I know there is.
女人啊 你需要有点生活
Girl, you need to get a life.
抱歉 我的生活在华盛顿
Sorry, my life's back in DC.
-这里只有工作 -听着
- This is all I got. - Look.
我和ATF一起查件案子 武器运输案
I worked a case with ATF, an arms pipeline,
一个摩托车团伙干的
uh, run by another motorcycle gang.
Ramon帮他们造了些摩托车
Ramon built them some bikes,
我利用他进入团伙内部 就这样
and I used him to get in, that's it.
-你和他上床了 -什么
- You screwed him. - What?
你准备否认吗
You gonna say you didn't?
好吧
Okay.
你先告诉我 你是怎么知道
Well, first do you want to tell me how you knew
McKinley偷了卡特琳娜飓风基金
about McKinley stealing those Katrina funds?
哈
Uh-huh.
看来不只我一个人有秘密
Yeah. Looks like I'm not the only one with secrets.
开始工作 好吗
Work. Shall we?
子弹是0.22口径的
The bullet was a .22 caliber,
然而更有趣的是我在枪伤里面
but more interesting is a piece of fiber
发现的一块纤维
I found inside the bullet wound.
我猜 纤维不是Fillibert的衣服上的
So, not from what Fillibert was wearing, I take it?
不是 上面还有少量的
No, and it had trace amounts
射击残留物 这意味着
of gunshot residue on it, which means...
是开枪后留下的 凶手衣服上的么
It came from the discharge. Shooter's clothing?
-理论上是这样 -对
- That's the theory. - Yeah.
杀手出现在Fillibert面前
Killer rolls up to Fillibert,
枪藏在他的夹克里面
gun concealed under his jacket,
-扣动扳机 -子弹穿过衣服
- pulls the trigger... Shoots through it,
给我们留下了碎屑
delivering us the breadcrumb.
还有
And...
呃
Hmm?
亲爱的 最重要的事情
The most important thing, dear.
对 我也许能恢复触碰DNA
Yes. Uh, I might be able to recover
确定凶手身份 我只是需要一点时间
touch DNA and ID your killer. I just need a little time.
我们没有太多时间 有什么
Something we don't have much of. Is there anything
你现在能告诉我们的 以便我们缩小嫌犯的范围
you can tell us now, help us narrow down the suspect pool?
可疑的时尚选择也许有用
Well, the questionable fashion choice might help.
纤维来自于一条金色的金属线
The fiber came from a gold metallic thread,
这意味着 要么是
which means either it was
-利伯雷斯 要么是... -那个
- Liberace, or... - The one motorcycle gang
美国钢琴演奏家，常以金色夹克和大量珠宝打扮自己
有黄金臂章的摩托帮
flying gold patches.
骑行帮
The Niners.
我在医院
All I heard
听到的都是骑行帮有多想报复
from the hospital was how bad the Niners want payback.
从我收集到的信息看 老兵们也是如此
Well, vets do, too, from everything I can gather.
但如果是他们炸了骑行帮的店铺
But if they're the ones that blew up the Niners' shop,
那他们已经报复过了
then they already got their payback.
除非不是他们炸的
Unless they're not the ones that blew it up.
我不知道还有谁会这么做
Well, I don't know who else could've.
老兵们准备要背锅了
The vets are loaded for bear.
我们查到匹配的炸药了吗
Do we have an explosives match yet?
-Sebastian还在分析 -很难认为
- Sebastian's still analyzing. - It's hard to think
-这不是报复 -是的
- it's not just an eye for an eye. - Yeah,
而且事情只会更糟
and it's only gonna get worse, too.
我们不能袖手旁观 让两个摩托帮
We can't stand by and let two motorcycle clubs
自行解决矛盾
take justice into their own hands.
你是指 继续自行解决吧
You mean continue taking it into their own hands?
问题是 我们没有足够的线索来得出
Problem is, we don't have enough leads yet to draw
任何结论 更不用说实行逮捕了
any conclusions, let alone make any arrests.
下一步轮到骑行帮了
Well, next move is the Niners.
现在 在我们得到线索前
Now, how do we stop them
该怎么阻止他们呢
before we get any more leads?
Ramon
Ramon?
什么
What?
你的旧线人
Your old informant?
我们看到他跟骑行帮有来往 不是吗
I mean, we saw him running with the Niners, didn't we?
可能是我们唯一的方法 加上Percy已经有一个卧底身份了
Might be our only way in, plus Percy already has a cover.
除了卧底没有更快的方法了
No way we get a UC in any faster.
我不知道
I don't know.
只是说说而已 她有卧底身份和路子
Just sayin', she's got both the cover and the chops to do it.
谢谢 我想想
Well, thanks. I think.
你认为你的卧底身份还是好的吗
You think your cover's still good?
是的
Yeah, I mean...
逮捕进行的时候我早就离开了
I was long gone when the raid went down.
而且 Ramon不是我们逮捕的帮派中的一员
Besides, Ramon wasn't part of the gang we busted,
他只是我的消息来源
he was just my source.
他不可能知道我的身份
There's no way he made me.
他能为我们提供有价值的信息
He could get us valuable information,
也许甚至可以阻止这个事件升级
maybe even enough to keep this thing from escalating,
但是如果你感觉不好 那我不...
but if you're not comfortable, then I don't...
不 没有
No, no.
Gregorio是对的
Gregorio's right.
我去卧底
I'll do it.
好吧 她得带窃听器
All right. She has to wear a wire.
一旦情况异常 我们必须把她救出来
We have to be able to pull her out if things get squirrely.
同意
Agreed.
Gregorio
Gregorio.
-你和Patton给她做后援 -等等
- You and Patton back her up. - Wait,
-为什么是Gregorio -也许是因为
- why Gregorio? - Maybe because
我在FBI做过很多次后援
I've done a million backups already at FBI.
别担心 我会保护你
Don't worry, I got your back.
那好 我们会在外围跟进这个案子
All right, we'll work the case from outside.
有任何消息马上告诉我们
You let us know the moment you hear anything.
收到
Copy that.
去带窃听器
Go get wired.
我得说 如果是我来做她的后援
Just gotta say, I'd feel a lot more comfortable
我会感觉更安心些
if I were backing her up.
好了 Chris 我想你现在手头的
Yeah, well, I think you got enough
事情已经够多了
on your plate right now, Chris.
再说 她们两个多吵吵架
Besides, as much as those two bark at each other,
就会处得好了
they're good together.
她们只是还不知道罢了
They just don't know it yet.
Blackberry Smoke乐队 演奏"Let It Burn"（燃烧吧）
♪ Well, if I had a nickel for every line ♪
♪ This town put on my face ♪
♪ If I had a dime for every time... ♪
我们收到现场的声音了
And we're live.
怎么了
What?
你在这个镇上停一辆FBI的监察车
You park an FBI surveillance van in this town,
会很引人注目的
and you'll stand out like a sore thumb.
哦 "天龙特攻队"是唯一的选择吗 对不起
Oh, and the A-Team's was the only alternative? I'm sorry.
出自美国经典电视剧之一，他们可以为钱卖命，也可以为正义而战
巧妙的流行文化参考 T女士
Crafty pop culture reference, Mrs. T.
但他们的工作方式只助长了我讨厌的人
Way they work, though, only encourage my nerdism.
哈
Ah.
你们够了啊
Y'all better have this feed up
因为我要和人接洽了
because I'm about to make contact.
♪ Just as long as I get out... ♪
对不起 但是...
I'm sorry, but, uh...
我们认识吗
do we know each other?
我去 你不是在跟我开玩笑吧
Holy crap, you gotta be kidding me.
你到底哪儿去了 Sunny
Where the hell have you been, Sunny?
-在附近 -Sunny么
- Around. - Sunny?
是的 他喜欢她
Oh, yeah, he likes her.
给我买杯喝的 Ramon
Buy me a drink, Ramon?
♪ To get a little behind and have a man ♪
♪ Come and take it back ♪
这是什么声音
What's that sound?
很肯定是接吻的声音
Pretty sure it's kissing.
我想念你
I missed you.
我也想你
I missed you, too.
你觉得...
You think...
是的 她上了他
Yeah, she screwed him.
毫无疑问
No doubt.
我只是 只是还不敢相信
I just... just still don't believe it.
两年了 发生了什么
Two years. What happened?
你去了哪里 为什么离开
Where'd you go? Why'd you leave?
我不知道 我只是
I don't know, I was just...
处理一些事情 你知道吗
dealing with some stuff, you know?
事情 比如说
Stuff. Like what?
说嘛 Sunny 我应该知道
Come on, I deserve to know, Sunny.
你和我 我们曾如此亲密
You and me, we got close,
然后你就消失了
and then you just... up and disappeared.
你甚至没有说过再见
You never even said good-bye.
我知道 对不起
I know. I'm sorry.
尽管如此 你当时离开
It was probably a good thing
可能是件好事
you left when you did, though.
之后所有人都被捕了
Everybody got busted right afterwards.
很显然 有人背叛了我们
Apparently, somebody ratted us out.
是的 但你没有被捕 不是吗
Yeah, but you didn't get busted, right?
没有 多亏了你
No, thanks to you.
关于这个叫
How much did Percy say
-Ramon的家伙 Percy讲了多少 -显然不够多
- about this Ramon dude, exactly? - Not enough, obviously.
嗯 但你没做什么错事儿吧
Yeah, but you didn't do anything wrong, right?
你只是给他们修修摩托车 对吧
You were just building bikes for them, right?
-差不多 -看起来Percy隐瞒的
- Yeah, pretty much. - Yo, looks like Percy's hiding
还不只是勾搭的事
more than just a hook-up.
别忘了
Neglected to mention
Ramon没被抓到 是因为Percy救了他
that Ramon didn't get busted because she saved him.
你打电话给Pride吗
You calling Pride?
不 打给FBI 我觉得这小子有问题
No, FBI. I got a bad feeling about this guy.
我要明确知道我们面对的是什么人
I want to know exactly who we're dealing with,
这也是为了Percy好 就是说
for Percy's sake. Which means...
如果你还没觉得有必要
if you haven't felt the urge
黑进ATF的数据库
to hack into the ATF database,
拿到卧底行动资料的话
get access to our undercover ops,
现在正是好时机 我就随口一说
now would be the time-- just sayin'.
但那么做不是非法的吗 Gregorio探员
But isn't that illegal, Agent Gregorio?
不问也不说 对么
Don't ask, don't tell, right?
那真的是伤了我的心
That really did a number on me.
我吃不下 睡不着
I didn't eat, couldn't sleep.
我骑车走遍了德州 内华达州
You know I was riding around Texas, Nevada,
一直到加州 就为了找你
all the way out to California trying to find you?
我现在就在这儿啊 不是吗
Well, I'm here now, aren't I?
迟到总比不到好
Well, it's better late than never.
你不能一直躲着她
Can't keep avoiding her, you know.
我知道 但是她也不能
Yeah, I know, but she can't keep
没完没了地打电话
calling all the time, either.
我得工作啊
I gotta focus on work.
工作不是借口 Chris
Work isn't always an excuse, Chris.
你对这个女孩有多了解
How well you know this girl?
一般
Not very.
这就是问题所在
I mean, that's the problem.
你知道Savannah死后
Look, you know how I used to be,
我成了什么样子
after Savannah's death.
那是段黑暗的日子 到处约炮
It was dark times, sleeping around.
这不是什么光彩的事情
It's not something I'm proud of.
我也迷失了自己
And it's not who I am anymore, either.
但是
But...
我真的不知道该怎么办
I honestly don't know what to do.
可我也不能放手不管啊
Still, I can't just... walk away.
但我不知道自己有没有准备好
But I don't know if I'm ready for all this.
我必须得问一句
I gotta ask--
你确定孩子是你的么
you sure the baby's yours?
他长得很像我
Boy, he looks like me.
时间也合得上
And the math definitely works.
这种情况唯一的解决方法就是
Then the only way to deal with something like this
直接面对
is head-on.
这对孩子的母亲来说也不容易
It can't be easy for the mom, either.
但是有一点
But one thing's for sure...
你不能逃避
it's not something you can avoid.
给她打电话吧
Call her back.
我去Sebastian那边看看
I'll see where Sebastian's at.
我不会给你压力的 Sebastian
Hate to pressure you, Sebastian, all right?
你有什么就说什么吧
I'll take anything you got.
我得到的结果 你可能不会喜欢
Well, what I got, I don't think you're gonna like.
我把简易爆炸装置进行了重组
I reassembled most of the IED,
要么嫌疑犯掌握了原始的谷歌技术
and either your bomber's got pristine Googling skills,
要么他有很强的军事背景
or he's got a military background.
好吧 关于爆炸物呢
Okay, well, what about the explosives?
还有更多的坏消息
That's more bad news.
它跟你从建筑工地带回来的
It's a perfect match to the sample
样本完全一致
you brought back from the construction site.
毫无疑问了
I mean, there's no doubt about it.
我不想相信这一切
I don't want to believe that.
为什么这些老兵们
Why would the vets come back here
这么多年后回来 要再卷入
after all these years just to get sucked back into
当初赶走他们的事件 只会更糟
what drove 'em out in the first place, only worse?
过去的恩怨不易了结
Well, old grudges die hard.
没人比你更支持
Nobody's done more to support veterans
退役军人了 Dwayne
than you have, Dwayne.
可你救不了他们全部
You just can't save 'em all.
我知道
I know.
如果是真的 这太令人失望了
Still, it's disappointing, if it's true.
一条臭鱼腥了一锅汤
Something like this stains the whole veteran community.
你打算怎么办
What are you gonna do?
就剩一条路了 逮捕Hogan队长
What I have to do-- arrest Captain Hogan.
ATF的档案显示Percy在两年前的一起枪支运输案件中
ATF says Percy was UC on a gun-running pipeline
当卧底
about two years back.
这位骑手 他只是修摩托车的
Easy Rider, he just fixed bikes.
偶尔也参与运输 但只是个小角色
He did the occasional run, but he was a small fish.
Percy跟他演了场戏 从而打入团伙内部
Percy played the player so she could get in.
就这些么 她的案件陈述里没有其他关于Ramon的内容了
That's it? Nothing else in her case file on Ramon?
没了 事实上 她几乎没怎么提起过他
No. In fact, she barely mentioned him at all.
你们在FBI那边找到他的资料了么
Did you guys find anything on him at the FBI?
只是些零碎的资料
Just some petty stuff.
我的直觉还是不变
Still doesn't change my gut on the guy.
他跟那些坏蛋混在一起
Hangs out with too many bad guys
但Percy却不认为他同流合污
without being dirtier than Percy thinks he is.
爱情真让人盲目
Love is blind.
是啊 又聋又哑
Yeah, deaf and dumb, too.
Pride 我开免提了
Pride, you're on speaker.
Sonja还好吧
Is Sonja okay?
Percy吗 好着呢 怎么了
Percy? Yeah, why? What's wrong?
Hogan失踪了
Hogan's missing.
我们刚刚去抓他
We just went to bring him in,
却在工地后边的沟里
found his bike in a ditch
发现了他的摩托车
behind the construction site,
车上还有新鲜的血迹
fresh blood on the tank,
还有离开的轮胎印
tire tracks leading away.
Sebastian在跟进
Put Sebastian on it.
你认为是骑行帮绑架了他
You think the Niners kidnapped him?
我想不到其它可能了
I don't know what else to think.
我们已经发出了Hogan的协查通报 现在我们正
We got a BOLO out on Hogan now, and we're headed over
开往退役军人俱乐部
to the vets' clubhouse to see
看他们知道或看见些什么
if they know or saw anything.
事态严重了
I don't like where this is heading.
如果骑行帮捉了Hogan
If the Niners took Hogan,
事情很快会恶化
things could get ugly real quick.
我们不能让Sonja被困在其中
We can't let Sonja get caught up in the middle of it.
我来解决 我们得通知Percy
I'm on it. We gotta get word to Percy.
骑行帮刚刚来了
The Niners gang just came up
找Roman问话呢
to Ramon asking for something.
看上去有事要发生 我去弄明白是什么事儿
Looks like something's going down-- I'll find out what.
啊 亲爱的 下一轮我请
Hey, baby, next round's on me.
呃 有点突发状况
Uh, look, something's come up.
我走不开
I gotta jam.
你走不开 什么意思啊
You gotta jam? What do you mean?
那些人究竟是谁啊
Who are those guys, anyway?
你不想招惹的人 相信我
Nobody you want to piss off, trust me.
我们晚点再联系
Look, we'll have to catch up later.
你就这么丢下我吗
Are you just gonna ditch me...
过了这么久才遇见啊
after all this time?
我还以为
And here I was thinking
你想知道我离开的原因呢
you wanted to know why I left.
她在干什么
What is she doing?
你要是现在走了 就永远都不会知道了
Walk away now, you'll never know.
好吧 你可以来 但是 你还带着吗
All right, you can come, but, uh, you still carrying?
靴子里的刀 你还带着吗
The knife in the boot, you still got it?
当然了 怎么了
Yeah, why?
千万别把刀扔了 Percy 不要
Don't give up your knife, Percy. Don't do it.
骑行帮要是搜我们的身发现了武器
Niners pat us down and they find something bad,
我们就完蛋了
we ain't going nowhere good.
当然了
Of course.
相信我 我知道自己在做什么
Trust me, I know what I'm doing.
不行 我们得把她弄出来
Forget that, we gotta get her out of there.
没信号了
The wire's dead.
我现在出去
I'm out.
你好
Excuse me.
老兵那边有消息吗
Did you get anything from the vets?
除了他们很生气外 没有了
Other than they're pissed off, no.
但你怎么会跟丢Percy
Now, how could you lose Percy?
你应该做她的后援
You're supposed to be her backup.
你在说什么 我们没想到
What are you talking about? We didn't know
她会丢掉通信设备
she was gonna dump the wire.
如果她要继续跟着Ramon 就必须这么做
She had to if she was gonna stick with Ramon.
她本可以不跟着他 让他走
She could have let him go without her,
但她是老手 她有办法
but she's a pro, she found a way.
是 但她以为你会保护她
Yeah, but she expected you
像你承诺的一样
to have her back, like you promised.
-好了 -够了 听我说
- All right, - that's enough. Listen...
好吗
All right?
这样无济于事
This isn't getting us anywhere.
不管怎样 Percy已处于那种境地
For better or worse, Percy's put herself
她等着我们去找她
in position-- she's counting on us to find her.
定位她的一次性手机了吗
GPS her burner phone?
事实上 一次性手机不容易追踪
Burner phones, by nature, don't track easy,
-但我在想办法 -好吧 尽快
- but I'm working on it. - Well, work faster.
如果骑行帮和Hogan一起出现
If the Niners show up with Hogan,
我不想让她一个人
I don't want her ducking bullets
躲避枪林弹雨去救他
trying to save him by herself.
呦 有人在么
Yo, anybody home?
请告诉我你有所发现
Please tell me you got something for us.
我会的 这真是个好主意
Oh, I do. It's a brilliant idea.
我觉得你们应该把血浆放在院子里
I think you guys should put a plasma in the courtyard.
Sebastian
Sebastian!
好吧 抱歉
Right, okay, sorry.
匹配了凶手夹克衫上的DNA后
Um, so I finally got the results on the touch DNA
我得到了最终结果
from the shooter's jacket.
我把它和骑行帮的DNA进行了匹配
I ran it against the Niners, which was easy,
这很简单 因为他们都有前科
since they all have a police record.
-你有什么发现 -没有
- What'd you find? - Nothing.
不匹配 也就是说
No match, which means
杀Fillibert的凶手不是骑行帮的人
Fillibert's killer was not a Niner.
但他穿着骑行帮的夹克衫
But he was wearing a Niner jacket.
对 因为他想让它看上去像是
Yeah, because he wanted to make it look like
骑行帮杀了他
the Niners shot him.
好了 另外
Right, well, to that point,
我也匹配了简易爆炸装置上的
I also ran DNA recovery
DNA采样
on the IED explosives, uh,
但也不匹配老兵中的任何一人
but no match on any of the vets, either.
也检查了海军和国防部记录
Checked both navy and DoD records, too.
所以 你是说这一切
So, what, you're saying that neither the Niners
既不是骑行帮也不是老兵们干的
or the vets are responsible for all this?
你知道 我只是个科学家
Well, you know, I'm just a scientist
一天到晚在实验室
cooped up in a lab all day,
但如果就证据来讲
but if we go by the evidence,
是这样 但是
then yeah. However,
证据同样显示
the evidence also shows
凶手夹克衫上和简易炸弹上的DNA
that the DNA from the killer's jacket
是匹配的
and the bomber's IED are a match.
-这意味着 -有第三方
- Which means? - A third party's
想让双方对立起来
trying to set 'em both up--
想点燃仇恨
trying to rekindle the feud.
但最终为了什么
But to what end?
他们互相残杀后
I mean, who stands to gain
谁能从中获利呢
from them killing each other?
这就是我们要查明的
What we have to find out.
你听说过这个人吗
You hear this guy?
有点嘚瑟 哈
Just the right amount of cocky, huh?
-20英尺 -我知道
- 20 high. - I gotcha.
该死
Damn it.
我买了啤酒
I brought beer.
来得正好
Yeah, about time.
那边发生什么事了
What's going on over there, anyway?
我不知道 我怎么会知道 我只组装摩托
I don't know. How would I know? I just build bikes, right?
是 只不过我没见你组装什么
Yeah, except I don't see you building any.
走吧
Come on.
不 等一下
No, hold up.
你把我带到这个鬼地方
You brought me all the way out here to paradise pit,
我想我应该知道这里要发生什么
I think I deserve to know what's going on.
我只是不想让我们陷入任何麻烦
I just don't want us to get in any kind of trouble.
我们不会 你是我的幸运符
We can't, you're my lucky charm.
只要你在旁边 我就不会陷入任何麻烦
I don't get in any trouble when you're around.
来吧 我们单独待会
Come on, let's go catch up in private.
我想我有所发现
Think I might have something.
回头打给你
I'll call you back.
区域划分图
Zoning maps?
我一直在想到底是谁
I've been trying to figure out who else
想让骑行帮和老兵们相互争斗
would want the Niners and the vets fighting again,
但我没有任何思路
but I keep coming up empty.
然后我开始思考 有人或许
Then I started wondering if maybe it was more about
不想让老兵们重新回到镇上
somebody not wanting the vets back in town at all.
他们不是在那里建适用住房吗
Isn't that where they're trying to build affordable housing?
-在Broadmoor吗 -嗯
- Broadmoor? - Mm-hmm.
在老兵们被赶出新奥尔良
After the vets were chased out of New Orleans
McKinley拿走了
and McKinley took off
联邦应急管理局的资金后
with the FEMA funds,
整个社区开始打官司
whole neighborhood went into litigation.
自那以后就一直搁置
Been left for dead ever since.
六个月前 市政府重启了那块地
City released it six months ago.
这时候Fillibert拿到了许可
When Fillibert got the permit.
市政府支持Fillibert是因为老兵们
City approved Fillibert because of the vets,
但盯着这块地的不止他一个人
but he wasn't the only one with eyes on the land.
过去几年 为了经济效益
Developers been wanting to rezone it
开发商一直想再分区
for commercial use for years.
老兵们打败了他们
Vets beat them to the punch,
把它作为住宅用地
kept it residential.
所以 这是一次土地争夺么
So, what, it's a land grab?
有人想要
Somebody wanted to
点燃仇恨
rekindle the feud
让老兵们再次离开
to get the vets to leave again?
如果老兵们离开了 市政府会放宽许可
If the vets leave, city releases the permits.
Broadmoor会重建
Yeah and Broadmoor gets rebuilt,
但不再作为住宅
but not for housing.
作为商用
For profits.
知道这些开发商是谁么
Well, any idea who the developers are?
我知道
I think I know.
如果没记错
If memory serves,
在McKinley逃跑之前
before McKinley ran off,
他曾将Broadmoor减价出售
he put Broadmoor up on fire sale.
如果没记错是什么意思
If memory serves?
这不是重点
Not the point.
继续
Keep going.
我想也是
Yep, I thought so.
公司联合诉讼
Company tied up in litigation--
Aufiero团伙
Aufiero Partners.
Aufiero黑手党
Aufiero... Mob?
本来是在纽约
Out of New York, originally, yeah.
所以你会知道这些吗
Is that how you know about all this?
这不是重点 但Ramon可能知道
Not the point. But Ramon might be.
我认为Aufieros和ATF那件案子有关
I think the Aufieros were connected to that ATF case
Percy就是在办那件案子时遇到他的
Percy was working on when she met him.
"勒索 武器交易 走私毒品"
"Extortion, arms dealing,
他们都被抓了
drug running." They all got busted,
Ramon属于哪一个
but where does Ramon fit in?
他没有被抓 Percy很肯定这点
He didn't get busted, Percy made sure of that.
说来话长
Long story.
他的名字从来没出现过
There's got to be a reason why
一定是有理由的
his name never turns up,
但他经常被抓
but he always does.
找到了
Got him.
Ramon Vargas Tony Aveda Leo Manzini
Ramon Vargas, Tony Aveda, Leo Manzini.
用各种名字 专门从事
Specializes in trafficking weapons
贩运武器
under every name.
都是为Aufieros做事
And always for the Aufieros.
怪不得Percy没有告发他 她不知道
No wonder Percy didn't turn him in, she had no idea.
很可能就是他点燃仇恨
It could be he's the one who's instigating the feud
为了Aufieros
for the Aufieros.
也就是
Which means, yet again,
她不知道
she has no idea.
来吧 Hogan
Come on, Hogan.
-等等 -怎么了
- Hold on, hold on. - What?
-快走 -别担心
- Move. - Don't worry about it,
-走 -和我们没关系
- Move! - It doesn't matter.
你怎么能说和我们没关系呢
What do you mean it doesn't matter?
你看 那个人被打得血肉模糊了
Look, that guy is beaten to a pulp!
我们得做点什么
We got to do something.
什么 等等 你到底在说什么
What? Hold on, what the hell are you talking about?
-算了 -等等
- Never mind. - Wait,
你要离开我吗
you trying to take off on me?
-哦 -你要这么做吗
-  Ow. - Is that what's going on?
-嘿 放开我 -不
- Hey, let go of me. - No.
现在 听着 我救过你一次
Now, look, I saved your ass once.
你最好别
You better not
得寸进尺
push your luck now.
我总连不上Percy的一次性手机
Ah, I keep losing the signal on Percy's burner.
要么是她周围有太多干扰
Either there's a lot of interference,
要么是她的位置太偏了
or it's too remote.
至少我们现在走的方向是正确的吧
Are we at least headed in the right direction?
她在运河边上
Well, it's by the canals,
这可能是干扰的原因
that might explain the interference.
我也还是联系不到她
I still can't reach her, either.
找到了
Got it!
Palomino打捞地
Palomino Salvage.
她在废品堆积站
She's at the junkyard.
很好 如果你联系上她
All right, if you get her,
告诉她我们在路上
you tell her we're on our way!
我在你后面 King
Right behind you, King.
我们来解决这件事吧 Hogan
Now we're gonna settle this, Hogan.
这还没完
This won't be the end of it.
你说对了
You're right,
没完
it won't!
利索点
Get it done!
把Hogan队长塞行李箱里去 快点
Put Captain Hogan in the trunk, come on.
把他带过来 快点
Bring him over here, come on.
无服务
好 现在把他带上来
All right, now get him up there.
把他带到台子上
Get him on the platform.
这个可以
It'll do.
放下枪
Drop it.
转过身来
Turn around.
慢慢地
Slowly.
至少现在我知道你上次为什么离开了
At least now I know why you left last time.
你是警察 对吧
You're a cop, aren't you?
对吧
Aren't you?
-Ramon 听着 你不... -快走
- Ramon, look, you don't... - Move!
老兵们觉得他们可以不尊敬咱们
Vets think they can disrespect us?
那么 骑行帮 我们动手吧
Well, then, Niners, let's do this.
你真觉得你跑的了吗
You really thought you can get away with it?
我不知道
I don't know what
-你在说什么 -不可能
- you're talking about! - The hell you don't!
启动它
Fire this thing up,
让我们彻底了结这个恩怨
we're gonna end this feud once and for all.
联邦探员 放下武器 立刻
Federal agents! Put the weapons down, now!
-别这么做 -跪在地上 Hogan
- Don't do it! - On your knees, Hogan.
我们带你走
Let's go!
Percy在哪
Where's Percy?
我去找她
I'll go find her.
别冲动 Hogan
Easy, Hogan.
你不想这样做
You don't want to do this.
这个人杀了Fillibert
This man killed Fillibert,
然后试图杀我
then tried to kill me.
这次我不会逃避了
I'm not running from it this time!
这不是你
It's not who you are.
这不是你当初入伍的原因
It's not why you wore the uniform.
让我们来处理
Let us handle it!
就像你们上次处理的那样吗
Like it was handled last time?
骑行帮没杀你的人
Niners didn't kill your man
老兵们也没炸他们的店
any more than the vets blew up their shop.
有人要陷害你们 你们双方
Somebody's trying to set you up, both of you.
你扣动扳机
You pull that trigger,
一切就都完了
none of it's gonna matter.
因为我们会阻止你
'Cause we won't let you do it.
后退
Stand down.
请吧
Please.
Ramon 别这么做
Ramon, don't.
放弃吧
Just give it up.
去你的 Sunny
Screw you, Sunny,
不管你到底叫什么
or whatever the hell your name is.
你为什么救我
Why'd you save me?
上次你为什么放我走
Huh? Why'd you let me go last time?
因为我很愚蠢
Because I was stupid.
我以为你是无辜的 但是
Yeah, I thought you were innocent, but
我这次不会犯同样的错误了
I won't make that mistake again.
恐怕你这次没得选
You don't really got a choice this time.
我没有吗
Don't I?
FBI 把枪放下 不然我就开枪了
FBI. Drop it or I'll shoot.
立刻放下枪
Drop it now!
如果我是你我会照做 因为我向你保证
I'd do it if I were you, Ramon, because I promise you
那姑娘不会放过你的
that girl ain't letting you go.
我说过 我会保护你的
I told you I got your back.
大家都去哪了
Where is everybody?
Pride的酒吧
Pride's bar.
他邀请了Hogan的摩托帮
He invited Hogan's MC.
他很可能最后会雇下所有人
He'll probably end up hiring 'em all,
就像他雇了其他老兵一样
like he hires every other vet.
-他能负担的起吗 -不能
- Can he afford to do that? - No,
但那就是Pride
but that's Pride.
Patton快被逼疯了
It drives Patton crazy,
因为他是管账的
'cause he does the books.
嘿 这东西怎么会在Lasalle的桌子上
Hey, what's this doing in Lasalle's desk?
你得自己去问"城市鼠"
You ought to ask City Mouse.
"乡下鼠"
Country Mouse.
是啊
Yeah.
你知道什么
What do you know?
我不想参与这个话题
Just that I'm not gonna get involved.
你还好吗
So, you okay?
我是说 Ramon的事
I mean, about... Ramon?
你应该知道我们匹配了他的DNA
You should know we matched his DNA.
也就是说他既是凶手也是放炸弹的人
Makes him both the killer and the bomber.
他还在废品堆积站
He was at the junkyard
给骑行帮提供不明枪支
supplying the Niners with nontraceable guns, too.
是啊
Well,
我真是会挑人 是吧
I sure know how to pick 'em, don't I?
现在你知道我为什么一直避开这个话题了
So, now you know why I kept avoiding the subject.
我不敢相信我这么愚蠢
I can't believe how stupid I was.
你不是第一个
Yeah, well, you're not the first girl
被坏男孩蒙蔽的女孩
to be blinded by the Bad Boy Spell.
没错 但多数女孩不会
Yeah, but most other girls don't
因此差点丢了性命
almost get themselves killed in doing it.
是 有些人有一段令人耻辱的人生
True, some of us just live a life of shame,
感到后悔
kick ourselves,
然后逃跑 你懂的
run, you know.
我们之间的共同点比你想的要多 Percy
We might have more in common than you think, Percy.
我洗耳恭听
I'm all ears.
McKinley 卡特琳娜飓风
McKinley, Katrina?
对对对
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
他就是我爱上的坏男人
That would be the bad boy
在我意识到之前
I fell for, before I realized.
不是吧
No.
-没错 -你是McKinley的妻子
- Yeah. - You're McKinley's wife?
曾经是他的妻子
Was his wife.
-哇 -离开他之后我就离开了新奥尔良
- Wow. - Left NOLA right after I left him.
也许应该再早点离开
Probably should have left sooner.
但我猜 就像你也是
Although I'm guessing, like you,
我们也许一直知道他们的真面目 我们只是
we both knew who they were all along, we just...
不想承认
didn't want to admit it.
活到老学到老 对吧
Well, you live and you learn, right?
希望吧
Hopefully.
嘿 呃 这个
Hey, uh, this...
我们不是在联络感情吧
wasn't us bonding, right?
哦 当然不是
Oh, God forbid, no.
很好
Good.